Guide to the Associated Students of Stanford University Records SC0009
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2006-238
  - Binder: "General ASSU Records - Campus Security Board Task Force, Operating Budget, Treasurers Handbook, Elections Handbook, Nominations Commission Report, Elections Report, Undergraduate Senate Resolutions", 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Binder: "General ASSU Records - Senate Resolutions, Nominations Commission Report, Various Senate Chair Reports", 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Binder: "General ASSU Records - State of the Association, Report of the Divestment Subcommittee, Operating Budget, Student Organization Sourcebook, Senate Resolutions, Election Results", 1986-87 (Box 5)
  - Exec-committee agendas, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Faculty diversity, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Student group funding, 2004 (Box 6)
  - General meeting notes with administrators, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Stanford fund, 2004 (Box 6)
  - GSC agendas, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Senate bills, 2004 (Box 6)
  - VPSA Org Chart, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Alumni Association, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Judicial Affairs, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Exec-Aide Interviews, 2004 (Box 6)
  - SSE Board Docs, 2004 (Box 6)
  - President Hennessey meetings, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Legal counseling policy board, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Greek housing board, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Guest professorship board, 2004 (Box 6)
  - ASSU newsletter, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Nominations Commission, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Religious life, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Stanford News Readership Program, 2004 (Box 6)
  - SSE Docs, 2004 (Box 6)
  - ASSU State of the Association, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Student leader dinner, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Student Transportation needs, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Third undergrad senate minutes disk, 2001 (Box 6)
  - US Students Association, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Exec Cabinet Applications, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Cost of Living, 2004 (Box 6)
  - "Community Center Issues, University Committee on Minority Issues", 1999 (Box 6)
  - Provost meeting notes, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Events and registration, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Exec aide applications, 2004 (Box 6)
  - ASSU Executive Bills and Receipts, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Full Moon on the Quad Agendas, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Alcohol Policy Notes, 2004 (Box 6)
  - New Student Orientation Files, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Arts Community Information, 2004 (Box 6)
  - ASSU Alumni Letter, 2004 (Box 6)
  - "ASSU Transition Information, Board of Trustees", 2004 (Box 6)
  - Executive Cabinet Projects, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Commission on Graduate Education, 2005 (Box 6)
  - "Funding, The Final Governance - IT @ Stanford", 2006 (Box 6)
  - Board of Trustees Committees, 2001 (Box 6)
  - ASSU/SSE Literature, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Executive Committee, 2003 (Box 6)
  - Building 10 (Box 7)
  - Legal Counseling (Box 7)
  - OSA (Box 7)
  - Senate (Box 7)
  - Mosaic (Box 7)
  - Queer/LGBT Issues (Box 7)
  - National Legislation- Patriot Act (Box 7)
  - Arts Grant (Box 7)
  - Healthcare Advocacy (Box 7)
  - Kannokada, M. Misc. Notes (Box 7)
  - ASSU Handouts (Box 7)
  - Exec Aide and Senate Assoc. Applications, 2005-2006 (Box 7)
  - Elections, Spring 2005 (Box 7)
  - Misc. Financial Records (Box 7)
  - Governing Docs- Constitution and By-Laws, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Miscellany (Box 7)
  - NSO (Box 7)
  - ASSU-University Interaction (Box 7)
  - Student Organizations (Box 7)
  - ExComm (Box 7)
  - NSO (Box 7)
  - NSO and Faces (Box 7)
  - Dining (Box 7)
  - RA Information, 2004-2005 (Box 7)
  - Dining (Box 7)
  - Community Centers, 2004-2005 (Box 7)
  - Communication Fee (Box 7)
  - Student Groups (Box 7)
  - OSA, 2004-2005 (Box 7)
  - IDA, 2004-2005 (Box 7)
  - Alumni Network Memory (Box 7)
  - Draw (Box 7)
  - Faculty Senate (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Elections Reform (Box 7)
  - Executive Cabinet (Box 7)
  - Acts of Intolerance (Box 7)
  - Community Centers (Box 7)
  - Reserves/Buffers (Box 7)
  - IDA (Box 7)
  - The Blender (Box 7)
  - Diversity (Box 7)
  - Constitutional Council (Box 7)
  - Student Groups (Box 7)
  - Diversity (Box 7)
  - NomCom (Box 7)
  - Undergrad Housing (Box 7)
  - VSO Website (Box 7)
  - Technology (STAC) (Box 7)
  - Academics - GERs (Box 7)
  - Graduate Diversity (Box 7)
  - Executive Aides (Box 7)
  - Student Advocacy (Box 7)
  - Guest Professorship Board (Box 7)
  - Cost of Living (Box 7)
  - Student Life (Box 7)
  - Room Reservations (Box 7)
  - Dining and Housing (Box 7)
  - Stanford Fund (Box 7)
  - Arts Advocacy (Box 7)
  - Cardinal Council (Box 7)
  - Laundry (Box 7)
  - Absolute Fun (Box 7)
  - CPBA (Box 7)
  - Bigger Black House (Box 7)
  - Student Space (Box 7)
  - Nom Com (Box 7)
  - Budget (Box 7)
  - Office (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous (3 folders) (Box 7)
  - LGBT (Box 7)
  - ASSU Miscellaneous (6 folders) (Box 8)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2013-046
  - YELL - Youth Engaged in Leadership and Learning handbook. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - GUP [General use permit, Santa Clara co.] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cycle [bicycle recycling plan] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Master plans (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Swap sales (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Publicity (PR) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advocacy (ASSU Committee), 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Legal Counseling Office (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dining services (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bookstore - Follett (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ASSU Banking Service (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Elections (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Eating clubs (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Stanford eating clubs working group (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Pub Board (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Diversity issues (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Course guide (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Advising - UAC (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ideas (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Grad housing (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Athletics (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - USSA [United States Students Association] (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Orientation (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Student initiated courses (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Face of America / Diversity (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Senate (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - University for Students (Nick Thompson) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Community Center funding (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Senate (1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Senate (2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - VPSA - Student activities space study - Joey Natoli (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Constitutional Council - applications, 2010 Jun (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Old campaigns (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - ASSU (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - ASSU - Audits (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Finances, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - ASSU brochures and flyers (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Undergrad advising (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Undergrad advising (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - USSA (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - University diversity (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Women faculty (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Campus democracy (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Service learning (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Alcohol (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - SJSU - Associated Students (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - SU Cte. on Land and Bldg. Development (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - C-UAFA (Committee on Undergraduate Admission & Financial Aid) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Academic Council Mtg., 2009 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Residential & Dining Enterprises - folders (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Stanford folders (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Orientation (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Communication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Financial, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - CUE (Campaign for Undergraduate Education) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Focus Area Forum, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - ASSU Web (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Special fee E-mails (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - New student orientation (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - GUP (General Use Permit, Santa Clara Co.), 1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - ASSU - Union (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Diversity (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Faculty diversity (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Commission on Campus Safety. Lighting and campus safety report (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Child care needs assessment, 2000 Jun (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - PENitentiary (Stanford Spoken Word Collective) [audio CD], 2007 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Phi Kappa Psi - Battle of the Bands [audio CD], 2011 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Financial, circa 1999-2007 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Election clippings (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ASSU nominations (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Midnight Breakfast, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Senate constituencies, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Meeting notes (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - ASSU Undergraduate Senate, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Senate standing committees, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Senate standing committees, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Senate, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Senate meeting, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Budgets (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Projects, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - SSE Board of Directors, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Divestment (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Submitted paper petitions (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - ASSU office space allocation (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Concert Network (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Nom Com (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Amendment, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Speakers Bureau (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Stanford Daily - spring quarter 1996 - ASSU articles, 1996 spring (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - ASSU Executive Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Graduate Committee Programming Board (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Graduate Student Council, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - ASSU Elections Commission (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - ASSU Legal Counseling Office (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Graduate Student Council, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - ASSU (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Brochures, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Leadership development, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Photographs (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - ASSU Archives (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Plaques and framed photographs (Box 4)
  - Consulate of Israel - Student Leadership Delegation, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Univ 101 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - CEO selection (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council Mtg., 2011 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Nomination Commission (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - SSE CEO interviews (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - SSE CEO interviews (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - ASSU Budget (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - ASSU misc. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Asian American Issues Conference, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - ASSU 25th anniversary, anti-calendar, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - ASSU course guide (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Academic Council mtg., 2010 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - ASSU misc. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - ASSU Leadership Dev. Program, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Accenture, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - National Presidents Association, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - ASSU misc. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - The Bridge, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - ASSU Speakers Bureau (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Stanford Concert Network (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Director's Award [Black Community Services Center], 2001 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Buttons (Box 6)
  - Nomination Commission (Confidential Report), 2006 (Box 7)
  - Posters (Box 6)
  - Cardinal Consulting: final report on ASSU, 1995 Jan (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - SSE Board (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Advisory Committee on Residential Education, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - STEER - Stanford Taskforce Evaluating Education in Residences (1 of 2), 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - STEER - Stanford Taskforce Evaluating Education in Residences (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - NCLR [National Center for Lesbian Rights] First Annual Sports Project, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Promising Practices: campus alcohol strategies (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Graduate Student Council Records, Accession ARCH-2017-202
  - Student Affairs, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - FC Budgets, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bills, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Audio, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - HEAEA, 2005 Mar (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advocacy, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Programming Budgets, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Munger, 2005 Apr (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Student Space Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - GSC Office, 2005 May (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - FAC SEN, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - ASSU/GSC Budgets, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - CA Grad Coalition, 2004 Apr (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Policies, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - National Association of Graduate Professional Students, 2005 Feb 17-18 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Transition Retreat, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Transition Retreat, 2004 Apr 24 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Agendas, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Construction, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - GSC Agendas, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 2004 Strategy Project, 2004 Nov 8 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Health Care Discussion Forum, 2004 Jul 16 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Health Care Discussion Forum, 2003 Jul 10 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Report of Graduate Health Care Task Force, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Graduate Diversity Coding, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - GSC - Diversity Advocacy Committee (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Advocacy (1 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Advocacy (2 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Governing Docs (1 of 2), 2003 Apr - Oct (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Governing Docs (2 of 2), 2003 Apr - Oct (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Graduate Academic Life Survey, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Governing Docs (1 of 2), 2003 Oct - Mar (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Governing Docs (2 of 2), 2003 Oct - 2004 Mar (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Governing Docs, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Housing Advocacy (1 of 3), 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Housing Advocacy (2 of 3), 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Housing Advocacy (3 of 3), 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Governing Docs (1 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Governing Docs (2 of 2), 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Governing Docs (1 of 2), 2004 Mar - Jun (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Governing Docs (2 of 2), 2004 Mar - Jun (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Governing Docs (1 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Governing Docs (2 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - GSC Alumni Contact, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Transition Retreat, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Nom Com, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Executive Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Minutes/Agendas, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - GSC reimbursement requests (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Funding Proposals, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Interior Design, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - GSC Orders, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Opening Party (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dedication, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - GCC Policies, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Vendor, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Grad Comm. Center, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Gift certificates GCC party (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Stanford Trivia (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Tax Advocacy, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Tax Relief, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Elections, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Elections, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Elections, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Special Fees, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Special Fees, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Health Care, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Munger Project, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Munger, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Housing, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Legal Counseling, 2003 May (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - ASSU International, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - GSC Internal, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bulletins, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - GSPB, 2003 Apr - Oct (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Proposals/Bills, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Funding, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Constitutional Council, 2004 Nov 8 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Board of Trustees, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - General (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Athletics, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Diversity Advocacy, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Advocacy, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Stickers (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Name Tags (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Colored Paper (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Academic Life Survey, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Faculty Senate, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - GSC Diversity Committee (Box 3)
  - GSC Diversity Committee (Box 4)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-246
  - Regulations for Women Students, 1937-1938 (Box 1)